SAMUEL DAMOLA JOLAYEMI

PropTech Enthusiast



CONTACT



samueljolayemi4@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/samuel-jolayemi/



https://github.com/Samjolas

EDUCATION

BSc. ESTATE MANAGEMENT **Obafemi Awolowo University**Apr, 2017 – July, 2023

ENTREPRENEURIAL CAPACITY

EMEDITH Entreprenuership

Academy, Nigeria

Oct, 2020 - Dec, 2020

DIPLOMA IN WEB DESIGN

New Horizons Nigeria

Jan, 2020 - Sept 2020

SKILLS

Estate Management

Microsoft Office Auto-CAD Architecture Google Earth/Map Google Workspace

Front-end Development

HTML CSS (SASS) JavaScript

Video Editing / Graphics Design

Adobe Suites

Soft Skills

EMOTIONAL INTELLIGENCE TEAMWORK COMMUNICATION

PROFILE

Samuel Jolayemi is a recent graduate of the department of Estate Management from Obafemi Awolowo University, Ile-Ife, Osun State. Throughout his academic journey, he has gained extensive knowledge and practical experience in the field of Real Estate and Technology.

His diverse skill set includes proficiency in Microsoft Excel, Front-end Development, and Cinematography, enabling him to proactively position himself as a PropTech Enthusiast. With a keen eye for innovation and a passion for leverage technology in the realm of real estate, Samuel am well-prepared to capitalize on opportunities that further enhance my expertise and contribute to the advancement of the industry.

EXPERIENCE

COMMUNITY SCRIBE | | WEBSITE MANAGER

Navigating with Noel | Jun, 2020 - Present

- As a member of the NWN tech team, I play a key role in managing the Navigating with Noel Website.
- Holds the distinction of being a Life Ready Individual (LRI0014) at Navigating With Noel.

WEBSITE ADMINISTRATOR || VIDEO EDITOR

TEDxOAU | Mar, 2022 - Mar, 2023

- > Built and managed TEDxOAU website in collaboration with a co-team lead.
- Successfully implemented online payment ticketing for the TEDxOAU'22 event, streamlining the registration process.
- > Took part in the anchoring live-stream event for TEDxOAU'22.
- Edited videos for the TEDxOAU'22 event which can be found on the official TEDx YouTube Channel

INTERNSHIP TRAINEE

Northcourt | Oct, 2022 - Jan, 2023

Contributed in conducting online data research and meticulously handling data input tasks.

INTERNSHIP TRAINEE

Niyi Fatokun & Co | Jun, 2021 - Nov, 2021

- > Proficiently managed office files and welfare operations.
- > Acted as an assistant researcher and intern, providing valuable support to the Surveyors at Niyi Fatokun and Co.

CERTIFICATIONS

Learning Real Estate Photography - Issued July 2023 - LINKEDIN LEARNING

Excel Essential Training - Issued June 2023 - LINKEDIN LEARNING

Master In-Demand Professional Soft Skill - Issued December 2021 – LINKEDIN LEARNING

Real Estate Analysis Foundations - Issued October 2021 – LINKEDIN LEARNING

After Effect CC Masterclass: Complete After Effects Course - Issued September 2021 - LINKEDIN LEARNING Camera Operations, Handling Techniques and Lighting Dynamics - Issued August 2021 - NWN SKILL TRACK